<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Cleveland Force Soccer Club</title>
        <link>https://clevelandforcesc.com</link>
        <description>Cleveland Force Soccer Club Press Release v.1</description>
        <item>
            <title>Congrats to CFSC 08B ECNL player: LAZAR IVANIS</title>
            <link>https://www.clevelandforcesc.com/Default.aspx?tabid=1217102</link>
            <pubDate>December 14, 2021</pubDate>
            <author>Luca Scarmack</author>
            <description>Congrats to CFSC 2008 ECNL player: LAZAR IVANIS on being invited to the US Youth Soccer 2022 ODP National Training Camp! Camp will be held  January 27 - 30, 2022 in Tampa, FL!</description>
            <enclosure url="https://dt5602vnjxv0c.cloudfront.net/portals/1093/images/announcemnet/lazar_ivanis_odp.png" length="128000" type="image/png" />
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Lehigh women’s soccer team announces 7-player recruiting class</title>
            <link>https://www.soccerwire.com/news/lehigh-womens-soccer-team-announces-7-player-recruiting-class/</link>
            <pubDate>July 14, 2021</pubDate>
            <author>soccerwire.com</author>
            <description>Lehigh head women’s soccer coach Eric Lambinus announced the Mountain Hawks’ incoming class of 2025 on Tuesday, featuring seven student-athletes from four different states and experience over the field. Congrats to Lindy Bobrow! </description>
            <enclosure url="https://www.soccerwire.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/LehighWSocRecruit.jpeg" length="128000" type="image/jpeg" />
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Cleveland Force SC and Internationals SC Boys Academy Join Boys Elite Clubs National League</title>
            <link>https://www.clevelandforcesc.com/Default.aspx?tabid=1102774</link>
            <pubDate>April 29, 2021</pubDate>
            <author>Marko Raduka</author>
            <description>Our Boys Academy Program is excited to announce our acceptance into the Elite Clubs National League (ECNL) for the 2021-2022 season under the Cleveland Force SC banner.</description>
            <enclosure url="https://www.clevelandforcesc.com/portals/1093/images/ecnl/ecnl_b-banner.png" length="128000" type="image/png" />
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Congrats to CFSC (MLS NEXT) alumni, Andrew Cooke, for Patriot League Player Of The Week!</title>
            <link>https://www.clevelandforcesc.com/Default.aspx?tabid=1089799</link>
            <pubDate>March 30, 2021</pubDate>
            <author>clevelandforcesc</author>
            <description>We always are looking forward to seeing the next generation of CFSC players moving forward to the academic institutions of their dreams, while finding athletic success!</description>
            <enclosure url="https://www.clevelandforcesc.com/portals/1093/images/announcemnet/andrew_cook-01.png" length="128000" type="image/png" />
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>CFSC JOINS GIRLS ELITE CLUBS NATIONAL LEAGUE FOR 2021-2022 SEASON</title>
            <link>https://www.clevelandforcesc.com/Default.aspx?tabid=1067404</link>
            <pubDate>March 16, 2021</pubDate>
            <author>Everett Palache</author>
            <description>Cleveland Force Soccer Club is excited to announce our acceptance into the Girls Elite Clubs National League (ECNL) for the2021-2022 season to begin August 2021 for the U13-U19 age groups. The ECNL will provide our top female athletes with the nation’shighest level of competition and will serve as the top of our player pathway pyramid with the ECNL-Regional league just below....</description>
            <enclosure url="https://www.clevelandforcesc.com/portals/1093/images/ecnl/ecnl_banner.png" type="image/png" />
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Denny Ciornei announced as CFSC Goalkeeping Director</title>
            <link>https://www.clevelandforcesc.com/Default.aspx?tabid=1066378</link>
            <pubDate>March 2, 2021</pubDate>
            <author>Everett Palache</author>
            <description>The addition of Coach Denny is an example of our commitment to providing an unparalleled club structure for all members/positions within the organization. Coach Denny shares our commitment and passion to empower intelligent, humble, and hard-working boys and girls,who approach goals with a positive outlook, both on and off the field. We are blessed to have him join and look forward to seeing thegrowth of our keepers and the culture of the program...</description>
            <enclosure url="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/G9Xaq5viosW2WbA-fhMRd3BGo0FdOVYGAMfdpZe_lpAxCcTtUtHFKOsdssNG2HlIbr-2s8kWtFw2XDkbjQ6N8PaMyaXjuAtcq57czWSkBjq4kUTFH_dsBZIql46vyYdCs4hAJU3q" type="image/png" />
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Cleveland Force SC Announces Intention to Join USL League Two</title>
            <link>https://www.clevelandforcesc.com/Default.aspx?tabid=971388</link>
            <pubDate>October 28, 2020</pubDate>
            <author>Marko Raduka</author>
            <description>Youth soccer organization Cleveland Force SC today announced its intention to purchase a USL League Two franchise in the coming years.As one of the top youth development clubs in Ohio, Force SC leadership is seeking to add both a senior team in USL League Two and anelite pre-professional side competing in the USL Academy League to the apex of its development pyramid...</description>
            <enclosure url="https://www.clevelandforcesc.com/portals/1093/images/0/program%20info/u15-u18/pre_pro_program_info_pb-01.png" type="image/png" />
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>